and I never want to be the parent like
I've had in the past like my dad who was
very um he was a he made he wanted me to
be a perfectionist essenti and out of
love you know he'd be like I remember
coming home with a 97% and he'd be like
this is great but where's the other 3%
and you know I had another sister to
come home at 75 and that was okay so
it's like he had higher expectations of
me and it it was out of love but he
didn't even understand how that affected
me in my career or in high school or um
in University if I got 9 9% oh my God
Natasha what about the other percent was
that good enough and I remember a
professor I'll never forget her who
taught me investor relations she said
Natasha it's not about 100% it's about
giving your best and when you continue
to do that just trust that everything
else will open up for you at the end of
the day you know employers are not
looking at your GPA to say did she get
all a pluses but I was very hard on
myself and I think even now as an
entrepreneur and with my daughter I do
set expectations as as far as her being
a respectful human being you know um
having some level of responsibility for
like her toys you want to play with them
clean them up uh giving what can we get
rid of every year I like to give back to
the community and so I'm just instilling
in her values that I know are important
and things that she's going to need to
know like we've talked about what's
happening I remember we were watching a
protest a couple months ago and she's
like what's H what why is that happening
mom and I had to share with her the
history you know of slavery and how
things used to be she thought that was
so
sad so I I believe we have to have these
hard conversation with our children and
not because we to we want to protect
them but it's really to set them up for
Success I'm always telling her Natalia
be confident who you are speak up like
for example um when we were doing
homeschooling they had this activity
with the kids and I've seen this now
like her school predominantly she's the
only you know kid of color in her class
um and that's okay so she has prepared
not to maybe see people like her all the
time of her skin color so forth but uh
the the teacher is asking them to do
what was called um like a guessing game
like what animal could this be and all
her friends were sharing their ideas and
she had it sitting there like she
thought I was a penguin but she was so
scared to say it and I was like Natalia
just say it it's okay if you're wrong
but at least you're sharing it and the
funny thing is she shared it and she
ended up being the
one and you don't have to say out of
86,000 seconds
stage was the final stage where they
[Music]
actually to see any
success media came out of both of those
things
[Music]
what's going on folks this is Ryan Perez
and welcome to go live and prosper um
I'm so excited um you know to be here
today we have an amazing guest I was
just on her show um and I think it was a
really great it was a great show you
know because you know what people don't
really ask me you know about myself and
it's really nice you know because I'm
always doing the interviewing and it's
always nice to be interviewed um
especially from uh someone that I've
been seeing and have been watching you
know I think I've know I I don't I
didn't know her know her I think I've
seen her around because we live in the
same city but um I think uh but where
I've actually seen our guest uh in some
of the business spaces that um that I'm
in on Facebook and you know I would see
her stuff all the time and I didn't know
she was from Calgary I was like what she
knows the same people that I know you
know what I mean she's in the Caribbean
Community she knows uh you know certain
certain friends that I grew up with so I
was like wow this is this is amazing um
you know to see what she's done with her
brand and with her business but before
we get to our guest um I just wanted to
you guys saw the trailer for The U the
world's first living documentary
um so I want to make sure I want to uh
make sure that you guys go to the link I
put it in the description you guys can
go to the link and you can excuse me you
can donate either $2 five $10 $100
$100,000 a million dollars um you know
completely up to you um I think that um
you know we've we've gotten so much
support from the community you know over
um over 30 I think I think it's over 30
um people donated to our cause and sent
a lot of well-wishes as well um you know
we've we we we started four years ago
and just as an entrepreneur brand and
we've really turned this into something
that um can really change people's lives
now the original hustle Zone show was
the go live and prosper show but at that
time wasn't the go live and prosper show
so um it was just called hustle Zone you
know but now we've expanded and you know
we've rebranded the show uh but we the
still the components of hustle Zone
still remain the same it's about your
story because so that's why we're asking
for your support is so that we can tell
millions of stories from people
especially in the um the the black and
latinx Community now go life and prosper
is for all community members so if you
have a business if you have something to
promote you have a book if you're an
author if you're a coach um you know
this is the the the right broadcast for
you and and and the reason why we're
different we're different because we um
we really spend time listening to the
person's story uh because you know
people didn't just become entrepreneurs
overnight they've had experiences um you
know I like to dig deep in um and and
ask them questions from a natural
perspective so we don't have uh
pre-written questions um I just want to
have a a conversation with our guest so
that being said let's get on with the
show now um if you guys haven't done so
already uh please share this out and uh
don't forget that we will put your
comments on the screen so you know all
you got to do is comment and if you want
if you have any questions or what have
you um make sure to comment comment on
uh on on on the broadcast and and we
will definitely mention your name Etc
and if you're watching on YouTube we got
super chats y'all if you want to send us
two three four five dollars completely
up to you uh we will definitely shout
you out um you know and uh for for your
contributions and and whatnot so let's
get ready for our guest now we have
something new normally I read the BIOS
but we got something new for you guys
today and we're going to have a video of
our guests so let's uh let's get this
going Natasha B Russell bcmm PCC is the
president and CEOs of NBR strategic
Solutions Inc a public relations agency
located in Calgary Alberta that supports
small business owners and corporations
with an effective strategy to get their
brand in the public high and stand out
from the
crowd she is also an international
Certified Transformation coach who works
with men and women all over the world to
support them in achieving their goals
and dreams through mindset
Communications confidence Clarity and
strategic planning coaching additionally
she is a certified motivational speaker
who enjoys hosting events to empower
women men and youth to achieve greater
success in life and business Natasha
obtained a bachelor of Communications in
public relations with honors from Mount
Royal University and has additional
certifications in life coaching
motivational speaking Health coaching
crisis and risk Communications and
online reputation management she is a
leader who is on a mission to make a
positive impact globally by transforming
as many lives as possible mentoring our
youth with the goal of making this world
a more loving safe and accepting place
on every episode of go live and prosper
we reveal the story behind The Glory
this broad is brought to you by B Thai
creative the web development firm right
out of Calgary Alberta this podcast is
also sponsored by Flix here an app where
you can edit your videos in the cloud
please see links in description for more
details
okay so we had a robotic voice you know
at the be at at the end in there so we
we're gonna we're g to work that out but
that's this the first time we actually
did that so um um so we're we're so
happy we're going to be rolling out a
lot of new features with go live and
prosper so you guys definitely want to
follow us in all social media platforms
but let me stop talking let's I'll give
it up uh for our guest Natasha B Russell
what's going on Natasha hey how are you
doing Ryan I'm doing
good so what did you think of that intro
I loved it thank you so much for taking
the time out and you know obviously
doing some research on who I'm about and
what I do but it was it was beautiful so
thank you so much for the warm
introduction I appreciate it awesome
awesome so now uh Natasha we you know I
always start this uh this uh podcast off
with one question and um you know people
will get mad at me if I don't ask but
what is your story now you can now what
that means is that's just a load of
question so you can go as far back as
you know when you were a baby all the
way up we're here to to to know about
you as an individual so you know what is
your story wow that's a great question I
was thinking I'm like where do I begin
with that do I start from you know
childhood or now as an entrepreneur but
you know what I believe my story really
is at a very young age I always knew
that I wanted to share inspiration now I
didn't really know what that looked like
because I knew that I just love quotes I
love positivity and my story growing up
is that growing up as a little child I
actually struggled with my confidence so
I had a very rare form of that people
don't know epilepsy of the mouth never
heard of I was around seven years old
and I remember sometimes I'd go to the
park with my cousins and we'd be playing
and my mouth would just go nut and I
couldn't talk I I could just it was just
drooling and I remember the day that my
mom saw me because as a child you don't
know what's happening and you're a
little bit embarrassed and she's like no
there's something something's wrong and
I remember her taking me to a specialist
I saw numerous specialists at a very
young age like I said seven eight and he
was like yeah she it's very odd usually
people have seizures of the entire body
but it's only her mouth it's very rare
so they put me on some trial meds and
long story short in two years I was
totally healed never had a seizure again
even to this date thank God but what I
was left with at like 9 10 11 was a lot
of weight gain from The Trial drugs that
I was on and so it really hurt my
confidence you know and uh as a kid I
was wearing like this little bracelet
you know like so people knew like oh if
something went wrong I was bullied I was
teased and so once I got over that
hurdle of you know being fully recovered
I then had to really work on my
self-esteem and boosting my confidence
and what shifted for me was I remember
at 11
you know my grandmother my family wasn't
religious but we went to church and on
Sunday I remember the pastor saying at
at 11: that you were fearfully and
wonderfully made and that resonated with
me deeply I was like Hey wow so I'm not
flawed so I'm okay like you know this is
exactly how it was made and from there I
call it is where my mindset shifted and
so I started to feed myself you know
positive affirmations and start to
really believe in myself and at 18 when
a lot of my friends were going to work
in retail to high school I was like I'm
going to go work in law firms you know
uh my dad used to say because I then
became to be the chatty person whereas
before I was so quiet and timid he was
like you should do law you need to be a
lawyer you're so my mom be like you're
so inquisitive you know and so I thought
before I actually Venture down that road
of you know investing in all that time
energy and money into a law degree why
not go work with lawyers and see what
it's like do I enjoy it is this exactly
what I want to do for my career and so
when a lot of people like I said my
friends were going into retail or you
know fast food and so forth I was like
I'm going to go work in the law firm and
they're like a lot of people like well
you don't have a legal assistant diploma
you only have a high school education
how are you going to do that but my
answer was confidence I'm like if you
actually believe in yourself and you're
able to learn which I believe we all are
then you can do it so I start to work in
law firms and start to share inspiration
I got the you know people like you're
always so chipper Natasha why are you so
happy all the time and I'm like well why
wouldn't I be we're alive you know so
even at that time Ryan I didn't even
know what my purpose was I consider it
purpose we all have one again I just
knew I like positivity sharing
inspiration so long story short spent
several years uh in corporate assisting
lawyers I knew that I didn't want to be
a lawyer but I loved people I loved
helping people i l sharing positivity
and so I went back to school U Mount
Royal University was like the first year
of being the cohort of you know at mru
and I studied I studied Communications
PR because I loved people you know
building relationships and then started
working in energy and I loved it it was
great I was making really good money I
was speaking on behalf of the
corporation you know doing media social
media like all the things I enjoyed but
there was still something missing and it
was like it wasn't fulfilling I I wasn't
being fulfilled by what I was doing and
so I started to look into what would
fulfill me on the last 10 years what
have I actually been doing sharing
inspiration why I want people to succeed
I want people to love themselves for who
they are be confident how they were
created and I started looking into life
coaching so I did my certification in
life coaching and then motivational
speaking and the two just mired well
together and here I am today continuing
to invest in my education helping people
to grow their brands on the pr side but
doing more of what I love which is the
coaching and the speaking working with
men and women to be confident in
themselves and their abilities and to
truthfully discover their purpose and
then go after their dreams so that's my
story if I were to
what an amazing story wow because I mean
we all have like you know I have a
client that is um um he has a disability
but he doesn't like to say that it's a
disability he likes to say that he has
chall he has a challenge and everybody
has challenges and some people have um
you know but some challenges are more
pronounced than others um you know
because and challenges we need
challenges to make us who we are and you
know for the fact that you started off
you know you know feeling depressed and
not having a good um like not having
good perception about yourself and then
realizing that you need to change that
trajectory in order for you to live a
more fulfilling life I think that's
amazing because there's a lot of people
that really don't get to that point you
know they go into circles into circles
into circles now were you when you real
when you heard that
message um and can you repeat the quote
again for for everybody yeah so at 11
you were fearfully and wonderfully bed
you were fearfully and wonderfully
baited and I was like yeah I am so I
don't have to feel bad about myself or
you know being chubbier than my friends
who are wearing you know I used to wear
like long sleeve shirts in summer and
like just covering myself up that I
could really just love myself for who I
was and so when I was able to really tap
into that confidence that assured
confidence my life started to change for
the best I was no longer limiting myself
or thinking I could anything I honestly
believe to this day if your mind can
conceive it you better believe it you
can achieve it so anything I've said
I've envisioned I've accomplished thus
far so I believe strongly in creating
the vision you know and then creating
the strategy and then taking action
where honestly a lot of people fall off
on because of fear maybe or you know
just not having Clarity or the ability
to believe they can actually achieve
what they want so yeah grown up as a
child you know I for me it was hard to
share that in the beginning like what's
my story like I struggled with being
confident but now I help other people
love themselves and be confident and
that is where true success comes from so
we just got to love ourselves for who we
are and every day I look at it as
growing like it's a continual growth
process you know we're not perfect we're
all imperfectly perfect and that's truly
what makes us so amazing and beautiful
that we don't look like anyone else like
we are we we are own what I call Unique
Flawless Masterpiece let's let's own it
let's own let own it I love that I love
that now like when you when you went
through that
metamorphosis how how did it impact all
of your family members and and the
people around you because like you know
if you're not you know I think as a
parent me being a parent you know I can
understand this the stresses of you know
uh of uh what parents have to go through
especially when children are dealing
with you know challenges uh how did your
parents react to you just building up
your confidence and and and how did that
change your your
life well I would say like they were
very proud like you know my dad is just
you know that type but my and my mom's
wereit of like a quieter soul but they
were just proud to know that I stepped
out of my comfort zone and I was able to
really share who I was unapologetically
with the world and you know I remember
the first video I made on and I was
nervous like people think like to be a
professional speaker we don't get
nervous we definitely do we get nerves
um before we go up on stage but it's how
we uh transfer that nerves into a good
you know performance you know sharing
our our comments or our key points with
energy and enthusiasm to connect with
the audience but when I did my first
video on Facebook I'll never forget it
was
2018 um Mid fall or not mid-fall mid
spring because there was a high suicide
rate in Alberta I don't know if you
recall in session there were a lot of
people that were committing suicide and
for me at that time I was still working
in uh energy I was very concerned that
people were taking their lives just
because they lost their jobs and I my
message was like There's Hope people
there's still hope from you have life
there's hope so I remember making my
first video on Facebook and I was so
nervous and putting it actually that was
2017 um and putting it out to the world
and people just loved the form of just
inspiring people to believe and have
hope and I was like yes it felt good for
me to do that it wasn't something that I
was looking for um sort of you know a
financial reward or a pat on the back it
was something that was generally within
my heart I just wanted people to know
that they shouldn't give up like never
the only time you become a failure my in
my point is that you only fail when you
give up so if you keep pushing the
needle regardless of what it might look
like baby steps they all amount to to
much so um for me I think it's all about
just continually pushing yourself out of
your comfort zone and and not looking at
what other people are doing you know
especially in social media nowadays
there's I look at there's so much false
representations people who are trying to
be something they're not or who are
gravitating to a certain lifestyle you
know you got to really find what what
you want what do you love to do what do
you enjoy what fulfills you because you
can have all the money in the world but
if you're not truly happy and fulfilled
and we've seen this with celebrities you
can and will there's people who've take
their life who've committed suicide
because it boils down to truly being
fulfilled in what you do and making an
impact in whatever way you
can now
I I I think that all of that is great
and I think that being able to um have a
goal to go after it and to have the
bravery and the gumption to you know to
tackle all the things that we want in
life I think that's important but for
the people if you get it all and what if
you're you get it all but you're still
not happy
exactly that's the thing is that if
you're not happy I look at it is there's
something that's not you're not being
fulfilled so are you chasing the money A
lot of people are just chasing the money
honestly like I just want to be rich I
have clients that come to me and say I
just want to make a lot of money well
why what's the why beneath the why why
are you doing what you're doing there
has to be a greater purpose than self
and that's and that's truly what I look
at it when I'm doing what I do it's not
because of course you got to be
compensated it's a business but is what
I'm doing actually fulfilling me does it
give me joy does it bring me peace to
know that I'm contributing what I call
my gifts and talents and abilities to
the world so where people go wrong
sometimes is yeah you can get all the
money but how are you getting it what
are you doing to get it is it in line
with your values and with what you feel
truly is your what I say your god-given
purpose or are you imitating or are you
creating let's be creators let's not
imitate what we see out there but look
at what we have and how do we share our
unique gift with the world you know I
have a little girl as well you mentioned
you're a parent and uh she's seven and
the funny thing is she reminds me so
much of me growing up she's so quiet at
home or at out on the street but when
she's at home she's full of energy you
know start she's starting to do her
baking uh business or wants to do her
YouTube channel and I'm like how do we
translate that to outside you know that
she can still be that bubbly outspoken
person that she is at home when she's
outside with her friends or at school um
but it's really a process people and I
think that we just need to know what we
really what really fulfills us
truthfully what do you enjoy that if you
didn't get paid for it you would still
do it but then if it's in a business you
should be compensated for
it totally now uh I was goingon to ask
you a question because you had mentioned
uh failure um earlier in the in the in
the
podcast what was one challenge that you
had to overcome just you know and I I
know we've already talked about a big
challenge but what was one in your
professional career that you felt that
you that that was probably the hardest
for you to overcome and what were some
of the strategies that you used to
overcome it all right great question I
would have to say honestly being raised
in Calgary alberd I've dealt with a lot
of microaggressions you know form of
discrimination in the workplace uh being
corporate being the only woman a lot of
times on the team of color being a
female and being a woman of color and
then having confidence like it's a good
thing but it can also be to some people
look looked at threat you know so I
honestly think the reason why some of
the things that are happening in our
world is because of the fear of the
unknown right um and so for me in
corporate from like I said working in 18
from law firms like big law firms that's
probably where I fit in a little bit
more because I like to back then I would
wear the corporate the full suits you
know and the lawyers wear the suits I
didn't really stand out too much um and
then I transitioned into energy I still
wanted to wear the Blazers and like you
know I like to look good and then I
would also be the one that was not
afraid to share my opinions with the VPS
or the CEOs in the elevator Hi how are
you doing so my personality would be a
definitely a bonus but some of the
challenges just dealing with the
microaggressions and the fact is that
you're only going to get so far or
you're only going to get to this Mark
you know and knowing at a very early age
that I had to be my own boss I knew it
like I knew that I was going to be an
entrepreneur it was just a matter of
when and so I looked at all my all my
learnings all my opportunities working
in corporate as a way to propel me for
forward to learn to build relationships
and naturally that's what's really
formed a big part of what I do now
because even working in corporate I've
SE I've met a lot of people who are not
so confident in themselves and that I
think is the reason why um what you may
be lacking you might Target someone else
based on the fact that they have it so
if you know what I mean like that
confidence is great but if you're not
confident who you are you might look at
me as a threat so my goal is we can all
be more confident and not look at each
other for the color you know the skin
color like based Judge Me based on my
personality my work ethic how I show up
in the sense of um my morale my values
that we can break some barriers and I
really want to see that the funny thing
is Ryan when I started my own business a
couple years ago now well part-time 2017
but full-time now for two years I didn't
even look like I had so many challenges
working in corporate in the sense of
like I said you know microaggressions
and oh you know you only get this far or
you know this is where you should stay
or you know this is not your area you
know what I mean um
that I realized now I'm like oh my God
like I forgot that I was you know Brown
like I'm I'm a woman of color I'm a
black woman right so even in Calgary I
had to start looking outside like not
just in local but like in the US that's
where a lot of my clients come from it's
that you know like I had to Branch out
and say hey like maybe Alberta is not
really the space right now especially
now what's happening with you know black
lives matter I'm so grateful for the
movement because we have been Limited in
so many ways and I and I also look at on
the flip side as me being the only woman
of color in a large room of maybe a
thousand people or 2,000 professionals
as my superpower you know like I'm here
so I had you asked me how did I overcome
it it was mindset everything is mindset
like if I were to come home every day
and think about all the things that are
not going right or not going you know
how I want it I would be in a depressed
state like many people can you know end
up being it but I chose to see the
positive in everything so this didn't
work out well what can I learn from it
or you know this is probably not going
in the direction I thought it would be
well how can I take what I've learned
and apply it to something that will work
to my advantage so I think people we got
to just keep our mind focused keep it
positive even in the rough times I know
life can be difficult I've had a lot of
challenges too I'm especi being a
full-time working mom and like I have a
lifestyle that I have to maintain for my
daugh I have a couple properties like
you know what I mean so it's like I have
to be self-motivated I got to push
myself forward every day I can't think
about who's potentially hurt me or who's
not rooting for me or what client is not
mine because I believe that who's meant
to work with me will work with me and
who I'm supposed to come across or you
know connect with like yourself I will
connect with them it's all about perfect
timing so just trust the process and
know that every challenge is really an
opportunity for growth that's what I
look at it beautiful I think everything
that you said is beautiful now I want to
get a little bit personal and not too
personal but I just want to talk because
you said something that really um struck
something within me because you know um
I have a sister that worked in um oil
and gas and she had similar experiences
being a a black woman that um is has a
strong personality but she's also she
was also an introvert she wasn't an
extrovert and I've worked for Xerox and
and I've kind of had that taste of um
you know on the sales side of things but
still it was really intense um the envir
was really intense and but when it comes
to women and especially strong black
women it's not only you don't only have
the barriers within the workplace but
you have it outside of the workplace
with relationships with you know with
people that come across and they see
Natasha she's all glammed up she's
looking good got the Blazer on and
hair's looking good you know uh but but
you're confident and you you're you're
no BS so when it comes to personal
relationships what were some of the
barriers that you had to overcome with
people you know um you know being or and
I'm assuming that maybe some people
would have found you intimidating and
maybe some people really liked your
energy but you know what were some of
your experiences um with that outside of
the workplace yeah that's a great
question Ryan um to be honest you had
you HD the nail on the head I I believe
for what I want to State there's a
difference between being confident and
being arrogant right I don't believe in
being arrogant I think confidence is
just truly knowing who you're you are
and owning your greatness so you know
for example like I have a I have a lot
of sisters I have two in particular that
I were I grew up with and some of them
you know these two because you know
they're in their teens they be like how
come you always like to wear Blazers or
you're so dressy all the time like
that's just who I am that's what I like
to do you know and that's my family
that's okay so um coming in from a
relationship standpoint on a person
level or even professional in your own
business yes we could be come across as
being intimidating but again I think it
boils down to we have to be more
vulnerable that's something I've
struggled with before is being
vulnerable because you don't want to
share too much but that is exactly how
we do break barriers is like okay if I
can be more vulnerable and share some of
the things I've been through some of the
struggles like I said from growing up in
childhood you know dealing with certain
things or in corporate or whatever then
we can find a connection so I really can
and I've never been a fan of like
dumbing myself down or playing myself
down to make people like me or gravitate
towards me I think that it's truthfully
those who are confident in themselves
are going to be able to have that kind
of relationship with me knowing that I
want to build each I want to build each
other up I'm not here to condemn you so
it's a double-edged sword Ryan like
that's a tough question but I would say
that we definitely do have our struggles
especially I'm very independent right so
um I don't need I keep saying this I had
a show and it's like I don't need a man
to take my bills right because I'm doing
it but that doesn't mean I don't need a
man I do want a partner but it has to be
the right one so depending on the kind
of for example person you're dealing
with I could be viewed as a threat or a
great Ally it's just on Viewpoint so
some of the struggles is yes you got to
be I I've learned to be more vulnerable
share more of my soft side and things
I've been through that people can
resonate with but I can't change who I
am and I'm not going to I can't play
myself down or not be who I just to gain
friends or followers or nothing it's
just not going to happen and that's
where I've just stayed true to who I am
and those who gravitate towards me know
truthfully I am genuinely kind and I
want to see us all succeed that's just
who I am and when you get to know me it
it speaks for itself does that answer
your question oh of course it does I
mean I think we all go through the same
I think um as entrepreneur URS it it
does I think people perceive
entrepreneurs very intimidating also you
know and if it's not intimidating people
perceive you as a maybe as a uh you know
Workhorse someone that is always about
business talks about business and
motivation and you know while other
people want to Banter about um you know
what's going on the The Housewives of
Atlanta or Etc right I think that there
is a different type of lifestyle that
you you know that you have when you
become an entrepreneur because you are
like you know the employer provides for
you but God provides for you when you're
an entrepreneur and you don't know when
it's you know when money's gonna come in
when it's not so you got to keep
yourself motivated you gotta keep
yourself structured Etc right so what
what is your
routine I love that my routine you have
to have a routine with especially if
you're an entrepreneur yeah I Rely
heavily on my calendar I always say that
if it's not on my calendar it does not
exist so my routine usually starts with
I wake up the first thing I say is thank
you God for waking me up in my right
sound mind so my affirmations keep my
mind right I then like to work out Co
was a bit challenging because you have
your now my daughter's working um at
home I'm doing homeschooling uh
transitioning out summertime so it's
then work out get my mind right because
I just feel good when I get my
endorphins up I can manage any challenge
for the day and then given covid so the
first half of my day it's play time with
my daughter schooling you know our time
then the afternoon is for clients
meetings and all that and then the
evenings it's home time it's time for me
and her get her to bed at a certain time
so I have time for me which constitutes
of you know reading a good book or just
maybe watching one of my guilty shows
which normally honestly I don't watch TV
during the week I don't really have time
it's normally on the weekend um and then
it's like okay taking a minute to like
shut my brain down and to just enjoy the
day like the you know the Gratitude from
the day what am I grateful for today so
that's usually my routine is start with
my affirmations get my workout in
quality time with the princess you know
meetings with clients and then back to
home Time family time and then wrap up
for me to have a little bit of me time
at the end of the day now in terms
of um quality time in uh when it's in
regards to
parenting entrepreneur parents you know
we're parents right we're everyone's
this pretty much the same we all deal
with the same um you know we we we deal
with the highs and lows of of you know
of parenting now in your
situation what
is how are you going to raise your
daughter knowing your past knowing what
you had to endure and and are there
expectations for your daughter to become
an entrepreneur are you going to set
those values or do you believe that she
should set those values for
herself well you know honestly I believe
that she needs to be the one to set
those values for herself when the time
is right she's still a little girl so I
I give her all she needs in the sense of
giving her the tool she needs to become
who she is that's through you know
coaching her just from Love and from a
place of where I've been but also giving
her the Liberty to try new things and to
explore like she already knows what she
wants to do professionally when she
grows up you know she says I'm a dentist
I'm a scientist you know I'm a chef like
she loves doing now the entrepreneurial
Journey when I made the transition now
two years ago to full-time as an
entrepreneur it took her a while to get
to the hint like oh Mommy's going to the
office because she's going to her own
office she's not going to see her boss
like oh I am the boss right she
remembers from going to corporate
sometimes we go outings or so forth that
oh she get to meet oh this is my boss
this is my team so it took her a few
months to get used to the fact that oh
Mommy's going to her own office mommy is
the boss and I think that actually
inspired her to say mom like I want to
start baking and I want to start selling
cupcakes and cakes and slime and so
she's just naturally gravitated to that
entrepreneurial Spirit but my my key is
to give her all the resources educate
her just love her poor and likees she
has a very good understanding of the
world around her and I never want to be
the parent like I've had in the past
like my dad who was very um he was a he
made he wanted me to be a perfectionist
essentially and out of love you know
he'd be like I remember coming home with
a 97% and he'd be like this is great but
where's the other 3% and you know I had
another sister to come home at 75 and
that was okay so it's like he had higher
expectations of me and it it was out of
love but he didn't even understand how
that affected me in my career or in high
school or um in University if I got 99%
oh my God Natasha what about the other
percent was that good enough and I
remember a professor I'll never forget
her who Tau me investor relations she
said Natasha it's not about 100% it's
about giving your best and when you
continue to do that just trust that
everything else will open up for you at
the end the day you know employers are
not looking at your GPA to say did she
get all a pluses but I was very hard on
myself and I think even now as an
entrepreneur and with my daughter I do
set expectations as far as her being a
respectful human being you know um
having some level of responsibility for
like her toys you want to play with them
clean them up uh giving what can we get
rid of every year I like to give back to
the community and so I'm instilling in
her values that I know are important and
things that she's going to need to know
like we've talked about what's happening
I remember we were watching a protest a
couple months ago and she's like what's
H what why is that happening mom and I
had to share with her the history you
know of slavery and how things used to
be and she thought that was so
sad so I I believe we have to have these
hard conversation with our children and
not because we to we want to protect
them but it's really to set them up for
Success I'm always telling her Natalia
be confident who you are speak up like
for example um when we were doing
homeschooling they had this activity
with the kids and I've seen this now
like her school predominantly she's the
only you know kid of color in her class
um and that's okay so she has to prepare
not to maybe see people like her all the
time of her skin color so forth but uh
the the teacher asking them to do what
was called um like a guessing game like
what animal could this be and all her
friends were sharing their ideas and she
had it sitting there like she thought I
was a penguin but she was so scared to
say it and I was like Natalia just say
it it's okay if you're wrong but at
least you're sharing it and the funny
thing is she shared it and she ended up
being the one in the class that got it
right so I said
W yeah I said if you didn't do that how
would you know so I've always encouraged
her to step outside her comfort zone and
it's something she's still working on
but I look at that as a positive she's
not the kid that's going to just eagerly
run to anybody or she's very observant
she likes to you know look at her
environment and then only will she then
sort of put herself out there so as
parents we just got to be open-minded
and not place our dreams or our
expectations really on the child but
give them the freedom to evolve and to
grow into their human being that unique
human being and then support them on
that Journey instead of trying to
curtail them oh you got to be a lawyer a
doctor engineer you know how Caribbean
parents can be it's one or the
other yeah for sure for sure yeah most
definitely now when it comes
[Music]
to I I
think let me I'm just trying to rephrase
this question here but qu when it comes
to like raising children I think it's
important for parents to have quality
time and I think as entrepreneurs we get
that quality time and you know we often
get busy and you know we're not time
blocking so we you know some
entrepreneurs don't get time with their
children and you know when we are having
that time with the children we're some
parents are not really having those
those those conversations about
money you know what I mean teaching
financial literacy and whatnot now like
how were you parented as a child and did
the parenting um and you don't have to
go deep into I just you know an overview
you know how did you know how were you
raised and then you know and then what
did you add as you became a parent like
how did things change when you became a
parent no that's great um for my family
is really big on like family gatherings
you know food love and all that my first
bank account actually was at the age of
13 and it wasn't my dad or my mom who
took me to the bank it was my uncle my
uncle bunny you know and I thank him for
that and the funny thing is now Natalia
at F like I opened her education fund
from she was born at like you know six
months so she has her education fund
growing um she has her piggy bank she
has her savings account so something
that I didn't really have at that
younger age I made sure to instill in
her because even now I talk to her about
waste you know um I think our kids
nowadays have this sense of entitlement
I don't know where it comes from like
maybe we give them what they want all
the time so they expect that they should
just have it and so sharing her with her
it mommy has to work hard for all these
lovely things you get to enjoy so you
don't get to just um want this and then
throw it away it doesn't work that way
and so I've been teaching her that value
of um respecting what she has you know
taking care of what she has and all the
money that she gets like we we put it
into her savings or even from her baking
business she started and I'll be like
for example we went to Walmart the other
day and she wanted to buy one of those
pancake um makers from Frozen and I said
okay no problem because she likes
pancakes like but you know if you buy
this this is $16 out of your your
account are you okay with that it's not
coming out of mommy's account and she
was like yes so now she starts thinking
more like do I really want this this is
something I really need so she's already
I'm really having those conversations
with her around money and waste like
money doesn't grow on the tree Natalia
like we actually got to start to think
about saving and you want to be this you
want to achieve like your education is
important so we went to the bank the
other day to do a deposit I'm like oh
and I bring her to the bank too so she
can see Mommy doing transactions okay so
she gets to that habit of thinking about
money and her own debit card and like
saving I think as Kirby and parents
sometimes we don't talk to our kids
about money no and and and that's
something that I don't want her to grow
up with thinking like oh like I believe
money is energy and what we give we get
back and all that but that sense of like
oh I could just throw that down the
drain no problem no natal you got to
Value money because money it takes time
to create it like we have to Value what
we come in what comes in so uh at this
age of seven I'd have to say she's
getting a good understanding of yeah Mom
it doesn't just come like that like we
have to work for it and as parents we do
need to have these conversations with
our kids and let them start saving you
know even if it's you know they they I
don't know if you're son I believe you
have a son right um if they you know do
chores around the house or we call them
good deeds you know um marking it off in
compensating them in some way or form
maybe it's a little of allowance or so
that they can save up and buy that you
know that hoverboard that they want for
Christmas or the puppy that she wants
that I'm like we're never getting you
know stuff like that yeah but yeah we
need to have those conversations so for
me what I've taken from my childhood is
like thanks to my uncle is starting that
savings account for Nataly it's been a
lot earlier than I did and I don't want
to be the the perfectionist parent it's
okay to make mistakes you know Natalia
said this what we're allowed to make
make mistakes here that she can grow and
not try to become what I think she
should be becoming but who she was
created to
become that's that's amazing now
speaking of you know of parenting I'm
gonna segue into
mentorship um I I really think
mentorship is important not only to
receive it but you know to give it now
if you were to Mentor a young woman that
was going
to come into your field now your field
is pretty competitive there's tons of
coaches tons of PR reps
and you know you're brave just by it's
just like saying you're I'm going to be
a m magician dad you know and like you
know because I I think like even even in
my career um with what I do it's it's
highly saturated so what sort of advice
would you give a young woman um that
would want it follow in your
footsteps H the first thing I would say
is really get in tune with who you are
as a person person like not what your
parents say you should be doing but what
do you actually enjoy doing like getting
in tune with who you are and then
investing I think a lot of times we
short ourselves by not investing in the
right education or getting the right you
know tools and resources around is like
joining groups that of people who are
going to support you I really believe in
your environment it's critical to her
success it's it's important to limit
your time with people or friends that
are uh naysayers negative they don't
have any goals they don't have any Big
Dreams that you surround yourself with
positive people so positivity investing
in your education you need to do that
and and you got to be able to actually
love yourself for who you are it sounds
so easy but I was watching this episode
the other day of like just plastic
surgery alone how many celebrities are
doing it how many people you know our
generation and younger want to you know
do Botox or get plastic surgery or do
butt lifts or you got to love yourself
for who you are don't alter yourself to
fit into what's Society expects from you
because that's your uniqueness that's
your superpower is that what you might
think is your flaw is Al is actually
your advantage so that's what I look at
whatever you think is your flaw turn
that around to work for you and when you
can look at yourself in the mirror every
day and say hey this is me I love me for
who I am this is what I want to do and
stay on task like don't get distracted
because there's so many distractions
around especially being a female like
even my business you know I'll be honest
a lot of males sometimes want to work
with me I have to you might due
diligence to say hey why do you want to
work with me is this really to try and
like you trying to date or you trying to
do business you know
so I've had to you know I've had that
gone that path too so don't get
distracted stay focused on the goal a
lot of times um I say this like if the
vision is there that means if God gave
you the vision he has given you
everything or he or she however you look
at has given you whatever you need to
achieve it so it might seem big and oh
my God I don't know if I can achieve it
but if it's there it's there for a
reason so sometimes I'm like oh my gosh
why why do I why did I choose this path
but I honestly believe I I was created
for this path and so every time I look
and say hey this might not be working
that's okay there's something else that
I can use to push me forward and so I
just stay focused on what is doing well
what is working and to the me the little
ladies out there it's really confidence
don't get distracted by what's around
you be focused on what's within you and
keeping that nourishing yourself feeding
yourself positivity knowing that it's
okay to be different it's okay not to
have the perfect body whatever they
consider perfect that you are actually
beautiful the way you are that's my
message own your greatness and own your
greatness own your greatness and stay
focused awesome so based on what you
just said what is your you what is your
number one because you've done that
you've owned your greatness you you
you're
focused uh what has that Focus brought
you in terms of achievement what's your
highest level of achievement that you've
done so far that's a hard oh my gosh I
had this question I had a somebody WR an
article about me the other day they
reached out me I was like what is my
greatest level of achievement and it was
for me it's every day honestly it's
every day when I can work with somebody
a male or a female a client and see them
progress in their business or overcoming
their fears or be able to accomplish
something that they thought they once
couldn't like your success is My Success
so you know we talk about business like
you know being heard on the radio that
was pretty cool uh da from B radio did a
you know shout out from me other day I I
didn't expect it it was great I was like
thank you you know um people are
featuring me on you know their platforms
I'm grateful for that but honestly for
me it's when my clients win like when I
see them really owning their greatness
or like finding Clarity then I'm like
I'm doing a good job like that makes me
more intentional more purposeful knowing
I'm on the right direction so every day
for me I look for a win I don't believe
we get to this destination even when I
have it all Ryan I'm still going to be
doing more that's my thing I could stop
right now and just you know like stay in
the nine of five and I'm living a pretty
decent life it's pretty nice I have it
like you know a nice home a beautiful
home a rental property you know the
material things that people want but I
want the heart things I want the things
that I can wake up and be overjoyed
about and naturally Ryan that comes from
seeing other people succeed because when
they succeed I succeed that's how I look
at it it beautiful I you you you just
had I loved being on your your podcast
you know I love having you on here I
just think uh you you just have a lot of
great Insight now um final question
before we get into the second part of
this interview before we close um what
would you tell that little girl you
know that was 11 years old you know that
got that had the epilepsy and you know
was going through all of of the you know
you were depressed you had you didn't
have the self-esteem what if you could
go back in time what would you tell that
little girl okay um what I would say to
her is that little girl that was lacking
confidence and then feel good enough
it's three words you are enough you are
enough that's exactly what I would tell
her and that's what I tell anyone out
there who's feeling like they're not
good enough in whatever space they've
chosen to reside in is that you are
enough and for me that was it when I was
that little girl feeling you know having
not feeling like I was beautiful or not
good enough was yeah I am enough and
that that's what it is it's just truly
knowing who you are and accepting you
for who you are and like I said it's not
competing with who's to the left or
who's to the right but it's looking in
the mirror every day and saying how do I
become better how do I become my best
self today and every day and if I can do
that that means every day I'm winning
and life is not about Perfection like I
I do want to note this like even as a
business owner it is there are tough
times people think it's a cakewalk it's
not a cakewalk okay it's not a cew walk
but that's why I talk about the why
beneath the why when you know what
you're doing and why you're doing it
that's what's going to fuel you to keep
going to stay motivated but also knowing
that it's an evolution right and and it
takes time to build a brand it takes
time to do great things so be patient
with yourself and um I've had I used to
have I would say days of feeling down
and out or like oh my God is this
working but I only have moments now
because my mind I'm able to like re I
was able to retrain my mindset and that
took me a few months to really work for
myself so that's like okay that happened
all right next what did I learn from it
move
on yeah awesome awesome awesome so we've
uh reached the first round so the second
round is the lightning round
okay exciting all right I just want to
acknowledge everyone in the room um
Monica was saying much love uh she said
uh great show guys yeah thank you so
much Monica Monica cardoo um you know
and and folks like I said you guys can
go I've also put the links in the
description for Natasha um you can click
on her website go to her social media
profile uh links are in the descriptions
and don't forget that you know we're not
just doing this for the love of it um
please donate go to our our grow fundme
account if you could donate even $2 uh
to help us build the world's first
living documentary and we want to
showcase uh the lives of black and uh
latinx uh communities around the world
uh because we just really really need to
change the trajectory of our news uh and
that's pretty much what hustle zone is
doing doing especially in this interview
today again we're not talking about
politics we're talking about individuals
that are in these spaces that you know
and some individuals don't even get you
know are not being put in the center of
these conversations but we want to put
um you know people like Natasha in the
center because they've done some great
things and we want to tell more great
stories so make sure you guys uh um go
on and and click those links to support
us uh so
Natasha talking or
texting uh
talking uh favorite city in
Canada canamore camore I love camore uh
favorite day of the week Friday Friday
nickname your parents used to call
you Tash Tash uh last song you
downloaded ever wow
commitment is it commitment by Monica
yes yes yes yes commitment okay uh would
you rather be able to speak every
language in the world or be able to talk
to
animals be able to speak every language
in the world yeah okay uh favorite
holiday ah Christmas and Thanksgiving
can I choose
two if I to choose two it' be
Thanksgiving yeah I love Christmas
thanksgiv I love for the food I mean
just give me the food and I'm good to go
but I'm vegan now so my family they just
make me broccoli and carrots and put it
on the side I'm like here you go so I
gotta go and make some cha and some Roy
and I bring it and I you know do my own
thing yeah because people don't caraban
people don't know how to handle like
they're like I I went to actually went
to um my uh Auntie's house in Edmonton
and I said I was vegan and she made
lentils and in our like cuz you know
we're Trinidadian she put pig pig feet
and or not pig feet pigtail in the the
thing so she's like yeah this is vegan
this is vegan
no yeah that's a whole new concept my
brother's actually vegan it took me a
while to be like hey now I just finished
my health coaching certification but I'm
like I see the benefits of being vegan
um and I'm actually a somewhat Dairy
intolerant since having my daughter and
she's actually allergic to Dairy so
we've actually have some things in her
home that are vegan you know so I'm big
on being open to other kind of you know
we call it diets but Lifestyles for sure
Lifestyles for sure yeah okay and um how
long does it take for you to get ready
oh depends on where I'm going but I've
been doing pretty good if my hair is
done it's 30 minutes 30 minutes if my
hair is done looks really good it looks
really good scale from 1 to 10 how good
of a driver are you oh I would say
nine nine awesome
fill in the blank um Taylor Swift
is awesome is awesome Michael Jackson or
Prince
whoa wow
um I'm gonna go with Prince you're gonna
go with Prince yeah good good answer
good
answer um at what age do you want to
retire oh I want to be able to retire by
40 but I'll still be working because I
love what I do by 40 financially I want
to be able to retire by 40 but I'll
still be doing what I do because I love
it yeah awesome and um two more
questions invisibility or super
strength invis super strength yeah it's
kind of creepy people walking around
yeah invisible like watching
you yeah I want to be seen I want to be
heard you know I think for too long
we've haven't been seen and haven't been
heard so yeah yeah and last question is
is it wrong for a vegan to eat animal
crackers it's a mindset thing you you're
eating the little animal that's still
sugar and flour um you know
what say it you know you got to do what
you enjoy you know is it wrong no I
think it's just how you look at it eat
what makes you happy within moderation I
love it love it okay and um and we're
done so well we're done part part part
two so uh you have some things that um
that you are um so explain to us a
little bit about uh strategize for My
Success workbook um so you said that is
now available what is that yes I
actually have a copy right here so I'll
show you the hard copy so this is actual
work
book and what does it entail so the
thing is I don't like to talk about
myself like I'm not a marketer it's a
very big difference between marketing
and PR but I do live a pretty good life
and I do consider my Su myself
successful because I get to live life on
my terms and you know do what I love and
work with who I want to and be you know
a great mom and all that to my little
one so this book entails how to discover
your purpose how to create a vision like
for your life for your business it talks
to you about how to create an effective
strategy which is your road map for
success and more importantly I give you
your sixes to what I call achieving
greater success right so it's all in
this workbook and the great thing it's
not a story about my life who wants to
have who has time to read life stories
right this is tactical information
that's going to actually help you move
the knal in your life or your business
and there's there's room for you to
write in there it's a workbook for a
reason um so I I literally guide you
through the whole process of if you're
if you're lacking Clarity around what
you want to be doing or you're in a
business you're in career or whatever
and your life it's just not working for
you right now you're not happy you're
not fulfilled this book's going to help
you to figure it out and then create an
effective strategy to take action which
is going to help you achieve greater
success so it's now available on my
website eventually I'll get it onto
Amazon at Natasia wrestle.com the hard
covers 40 bucks and the E version is 20
so you literally just go on to shop and
you can order right now wow so folks you
guys heard that you guys make sure to go
uh to her website I think I spelled it
right um yes Natasha BR russell.com and
let's talk a little bit about um tell us
a little bit about MBR group coaching
boss up and communicate with confidence
and I didn't I cut that off I'm so sorry
that's okay go ahead okay so one thing
I've learned in my business so far is a
lot of people like I essentially I work
with a lot of business owners you know
um with the coaching but there's been a
lot of people who are not in business
yet or who want to start their own
business or just individuals who are
lacking confidence believe it or not men
lack confidence too I do have like a
50-50 ratio inclin between men and women
um but I've realized that now especially
given the pandemic a lot of people can't
afford my services for one-on-one
coaching so I've now created group
coaching programs where you can still
get a great experience working with me
um for a shorter limited time 30 minutes
after you've done a session but you can
come in at a lower price point and still
get good content to either one the
bossup is essentially how to start your
own business how to create your
marketing strategy what you need in your
website content like everything I give
you the tools I just don't do it for you
so you get you get your road map for
business like your business plan
essentially and then communicate with
confidence which has been you I've
started doing webinars around it people
love it it's now in a group coaching
format where you can learn how do I
boost my confidence how do I overcome
fears or how are some things that I've
had in my childhood you know I have
clients who have dealt with bullying or
parents things that their parents may
have said that they didn't even know
stuck with them as a child or you know
friends that have been holding them back
and preventing them from asking for that
raise and getting that jye career or you
know showing up for themselves the way
they should that program is going to
help you do just that communicate with
confidence so those are my two new group
coaching programs and you can learn more
about them on at Natasha russell.com
oh yeah make sure you guys
go and then the last thing you you know
um I heard through the grap Vine that
you are starting a youth mentorship
program yeah so one of the my things
that I'm going to be doing eventually is
is you know I'll leave that for when I I
don't like to talk about things till
they come to fruition so I'm going to
park that but I'm now part of the
Calgary black Chambers it's a nonprofit
organization located in Calgary Alberta
and and it's a it's a bunch of
professionals you know of people of
color men women uh business owners
accountants lawyers doctors you name it
and um John Collins I don't know if you
know who he is but he used to play you
know uh football and now he's the
president of this nonprofit so Calgary
black Chambers I've been honored to join
them now as their oversight consultant
and we're working on a youth mentorship
program so we want to make sure that we
can mentor you know our our women our
little girls or little boys of color you
know diver no matter where you're from
to help them get the skills to build
their confidence to get into the
workplace professional skills career
building um talking to them about things
that might be uncomfortable
conversations that you they may not want
to have with their parents but may have
to just be there for them and support
them on that journey to achieving
greater success in careers in corporate
world you know whatever it may be that
they want to achieve so that's what
we're working on now and that's quite
exciting because you know why especially
being a parent our kids are the future
you know I did a workshop the other day
um and I was asking these kids that
around the age of like nine to 19 uh all
kids of color black kids and I was like
how many of you guys are leaders and
literally only one of them raised their
hands at about 15 kids and I said you
guys are all leaders you got to start
thinking like that right having that
mindset not being limited don't have
that limited mentality so I'm really big
on boosting our kids and because they
are going to be leading the future and
we need them to have those those certain
values confidence ability to communicate
effectively uh so that they can show up
for who they are and share their
greatness with the world so I'm really
big on mentorship and I I love it and I
do it often and it's something I
actually don't charge for because there
are kids so that's one of the programs
that are sort of
complimentary awesome that's amazing
that's amazing so
folks make sure you guys check out
Natasha go to her website Natasia
russell.com this was fantastic interview
thank you so much uh for coming into the
go live and prosper show what did you
think about the experience oh I love it
I'm like what tool are you using I love
the introduction like I I probably even
talked a lot about this but um when you
came on to my show the NBR show um which
people probably know is I'm passionate
about talking obviously I never used to
be the communicator but really
connecting with entrepreneurs like
yourself Ryan who are doing great things
in our community and who are not afraid
to share with others about what they're
doing and so your platform I love the
setup I love that you're so professional
we had soundcheck before people you know
the whole um commercial that you did for
myself and for your show and just your
story too inspired me like how you
talked about um being a bit add or you
know and having all that how you use
that to propel you forward where I think
that's the thing people is that we got
to start sharing our stories and not
feel like we don't have a voice or who
cares what people think I remember
someone told me this like what other
people think about you is none of your
business so to answer your question go
live and prosper hustle zone I'm so
excited to be a part of your your your
show today and I'm excited to see what
you're going to do for our community and
for all those who are really looking for
a platform to share their stories and to
talk about why they do what they do so
thank you so much for having me I'm so
appreciated most definitely so the last
thing that we got to do the uh on all of
our hustles shows we do a um a a step
because I used to be a hip hop used to
be a rapper we do a call and response so
I'm gonna say uh welcome to the and then
I need you to scream as loud as you can
hustle zone so are you ready Natasha I'm
ready okay welcome to the
H awesome than thank you so much thank
you so much so folks this was amazing
this was an amazing interview with
Natasha um you know and she's right in
my community like I said when I saw her
her her content I think it was in the
black content creators group or
something I saw her somewhere you know
she was just she was always posting she
was just putting herself out there and
you know what this is what I tell my
clients when you are going to get
into um business for your business for
yourself especially if you are a
professional that has a service to build
trust you have to have a great uh uh one
of the number one things I tell my
clients is you have to have a great head
shot she has great HUD shots you know
she's professional she has her logos
she's ready for Branding everything you
know it's the full package you see
picture of the things that are like with
her setup you see the things that are
important she had a picture of her kid
she had a picture of her her her
certifications you know this is how you
you know because especially when we're
in this type of business it's really
hard to develop trust and you know
Natasha did everything she has all the
pillars in order for her to propel her
business so that people can take her
seriously and you know she is really
professional but she's also willing to
have these conversations and so I
appreciate Natasha for coming in
um on the show uh that was amazing and
um you guys if you are late because I
know some of you guys are make sure you
guys check the replay and um the replay
you guys will be able to go to YouTube
and watch it there and then it'll also
this this broadcast will be on Spotify
and all the major um uh podcasting sites
like apple music and and whatnot so you
guys make sure to check it out and um
you know and make sure you guys again if
you're looking for coaching uh you know
PR uh she does a lot of things not just
those two uh make sure to go check out
her website um and like I said you guys
got to go check out this workbook okay
it's $20 um online and $40 for the hard
copy strategize for My Success check
that out and um you know and if you know
because there's different types of like
even with my company there's different
types packages you know depending on
your level of commitment and you know
this is an amazing coaching uh package
the MBR uh uh group coaching um you
gotta boss up don't take this opport you
know because things are going to change
folks you know once CO's gone and once
the economy goes back up again you may
not be able to get these opportunities I
would really honestly um uh uh I'm
trying to convince you guys to go and
and and check that out because um you
know from what I've seen and what I've
researched you know she's amazing and
she's going to do right by you so um I
want to thank my guests for again coming
on here this was was this was amazing
and and then don't forget go fundme.com
forf hustles TV you know $2 $100
$100,000 a million dollars however you
guys want to support hustel Zone TV I
just think it's so important we support
so many people we support so much
negative content um within our community
let's promote something that is going to
change the trajectory so that people and
I don't you know I personally don't
think it's always about um how people
perceive us because you know we are who
we are as a people as a group as a
community but you know I think that it's
important for us to also showcase the
beauty the beauty of our community and
this interview was just a good example
for that so and this is brought to you
guys by bowai creative this is my
marketing company you know we do
everything from Brand consultation to uh
web development to graphic design you
name it if you're in the need for any of
those Services make sure you guys go to
Bai creative.com and let me just pull up
that website make sure you guys visit
ww. BAC creative.com
and um you know we'll help you with any
of your need needs I give I give out a
free consultation is 15minute
consultation and 30 minute free
consultation if you do a video
testimonial so um make sure to check
check us out at bowai creative.com thank
you much love and um and oh tomorrow we
have
um hustle Zone
exclusiva let me CH hold on hold on hold
on hold let me change this let me change
this change this Banner uh hustle next
exclusiva with Monica black diamond and
Ryan Perez tomorrow we are going to be
interviewing a an artist um out of the
states his name is Adrien truth um he is
an upcoming artist that you know I've
already heard his song on a few videos
on YouTube and and whatnot he's a great
singer you guys want to check it out and
then we have an artist on Saturday at
the same time 5:00 P PM Mountain
Standard Time or 7 PM Eastern Standard
Time um we have um
uh Jason lamcraft uh he is going to he
is an amazing artist he was on the the
hustle own show the Monica Black Diamond
show before but but we're bringing him
back so make sure you guys check that
out and we got all kinds of people lined
up for hustles own and exclusiva and
some celebras and I want not gonna
mention name someone that used to uh I'm
not going to say it I'm not gonna say it
anyways I'm gone love you guys have a
good one talk to you later bye